sup everyone Tamers12345 one two three four
five here just want to let you all know
that I am going to be holding an
interview this weekend well I will be
interviewed and I will be answering some
questions that my fans want to know
about me on videos so comment down below
with any questions you want to ask about
me about my friends like Sonic Manic and
Sonia in them or whatever just comment
down below and all answer all of them in
the upcoming interview this this weekend
also make sure to make sure to comment
really fast what you want to ask because
obviously I'm so popular I'm going to
being so just so many questions that i
may not be able to get them all done the
time well I may not be able to answer
all of them so please ask fast and if
you will be up in next few days